Guide to the E. L. Wolven Glass Plate Negative Collection, 1897-1944
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series I. Athletics, 1902-1940
  - Field Hockey
    - Field hockey captains — Vassar varsity field hockey team captain Elida Griffin (VC 1932) and captain of the All-Scottish team with a Scottish terrier dog, 1931 Nov (Box 25 [package122c])
    - Field hockey game — Vassar varsity field hockey team playing the All-Scottish team, 1931 Nov (Box 38 [Box272_023])
    - Field hockey game, Vassar College and Yale University — Group photograph of Vassar and Yale field hockey players and Vassar's mascot, a goat, on Sunset Hill, 1931 Nov (Box 10 [Package081_009])
    - Field hockey game, Vassar College and Yale University — Vassar field hockey players in a game against Yale men on Sunset Hill, 1931 Nov (Box 38 [Box272_007])
    - Field hockey game, Vassar College and Yale University — Vassar field hockey players in a game against Yale men on Sunset Hill, 1931 Nov (Box 38 [Box272_020])
    - Field hockey game, Vassar College and Yale University — Vassar field hockey players in a game against Yale men on Sunset Hill, 1931 Nov (Box 10 [Package081_001])
    - Field hockey game, Vassar College and Yale University — Vassar field hockey players in a game against Yale men on Sunset Hill, 1931 Nov (Box 10 [Package081_004])
    - Field hockey game, Vassar College and Yale University — Vassar field hockey players in a game against Yale men on Sunset Hill, 1931 Nov (Box 10 [Package081_005])
    - Field hockey game, Vassar College and Yale University — Vassar field hockey players in a game against Yale men on Sunset Hill, 1931 Nov (Box 10 [Package081_006])
    - Field hockey team portrait — Class of 1934 lacrosse team, 1933 (Box 65/66 [207_24])
    - Field hockey team portrait — Class of 1935 lacrosse team, 1933 (Box 65/66 [207_05])
    - Field hockey team portrait — Class of 1936 lacrosse team, 1933 (Box 65/66 [207_04])
    - Field hockey team portrait — Class of 1937 lacrosse team, 1933 (Box 65/66 [207_03])
    - Field Hockey team portrait — Class of 1936 Field Hockey Team, 1933 Apr (Box 52 [Package64_008])
  - Lacrosse
    - Lacrosse team portrait — Class of 1932 lacrosse team, 1931 (Box 69 [213_04])
    - Lacrosse team portrait — Class of 1932 lacrosse team, 1931 (Box 69 [213_11])
    - Lacrosse team portrait — Class of 1933 lacrosse team, 1931 (Box 69 [213_05])
    - Lacrosse team portrait — Class of 1934 lacrosse team, 1931 (Box 69 [213_18])
    - Lacrosse team portrait — Class of 1935 lacrosse team, 1931 (Box 69 [213_14])
    - Lacrosse team portrait — Class of 1935 lacrosse team, 1931 (Box 69 [213_19])
    - Lacrosse team portrait — Junior Varsity lacrosse team, 1931 (Box 69 [213_16])
    - Lacrosse team portrait — Junior Varsity lacrosse team, 1931 (Box 69 [213_17])
    - Lacrosse team portrait — Varsity lacrosse team, 1931 (Box 69 [213_13])
    - Lacrosse team portrait — Varsity lacrosse team, 1931 (Box 69 [213_15])
    - Lacrosse team portrait — Class of 1933 Lacrosse Team, 1933 Apr (Box 52 [Package64_003])
    - Lacrosse team portrait — Class of 1934 Lacrosse Team, 1933 Apr (Box 52 [Package64_004])
    - Lacrosse team portrait — Class of 1935 Lacrosse Team, 1933 Apr (Box 52 [Package64_010])
    - Lacrosse team portrait — Varsity or Junior Varsity lacrosse team, perhaps on Sports Day, 1936 (Box 9 [Package038_003])
    - Lacrosse team portrait — Varsity or Junior Varsity lacrosse team, perhaps on Sports Day, 1936 (Box 9 [Package038_004])
  - Miscellaneous Sports and Activities
    - Athletic event — Unidentified athletic event, possibly track or field hockey, 1920s (Box 38 [Box272_021])
    - Goat, Vassar College mascot — A goat used briefly as the Vassar College mascot, including at a field hockey game against Yale men on Sunset Hill, 1931 Nov (Box 24/25[package 121e])
    - Horse and rider jumping — Horse and unidentified rider jumping a stone wall, 1910-1940 (Box 42/43 [Box278_017])
    - Ice Hockey — Students playing ice hockey on Vassar Lake, 1913 (Box 27 [package151j])
    - Ice hockey game — Ice hockey game on Sunset Lake, possibly part of Winter Carnival, 1915-1916 (Box 38 [Box272_008])
    - Ice skating on Vassar Lake — Several people ice skating on Vassar Lake, 1910s (Box 3 [Package013_008])
    - Party in the Alumnae Gymnasium — Students sitting on the floor in the Alumnae Gymnasium, some wearing athletic uniforms. Could be a celebration of the Athletic Association, 1933 (Box 67 [210_14])
    - Unidentified athletic event — Student drawing chalk lines on the Athletic Field at an unidentified athletic event, which included members of the Class of 1921 and the Class of 1922, 1918-1921 (Box 35 [Box267_001])
    - Unidentified athletic event — Student drawing chalk lines on the Athletic Field at an unidentified athletic event, which included members of the Class of 1921 and the Class of 1922, 1918-1921 (Box 35/36 [Box268_014])
    - Unidentified athletic event — Student drawing chalk lines on the Athletic Field at an unidentified athletic event, which included members of the Class of 1921 and the Class of 1922, 1918-1921 (Box 36 [Box269_023])
    - Unidentified athletic event — Student drawing chalk lines on the Athletic Field at an unidentified athletic event, which included members of the Class of 1921 and the Class of 1922, 1918-1921 (Box 37/38 [Box271_013])
    - Unidentified athletic event — Students passing basketballs on the Athletic Field at an unidentified athletic event, which included members of the Class of 1921, 1918-1921 (Box 33 [Box264_006])
    - Unidentified athletic event — Unidentified athletic event with hurdles, including members of the Class of 1921 and the Class of 1922, 1918-1921 (Box 39 [Box273_007])
  - Sports Day
    - Sports Day — Discus practice at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 14 [Package093_001])
    - Sports Day — Discus practice at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 14 [Package093_013])
    - Sports Day — Hurdles race at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 39 [Box273_022])
    - Sports Day — Hurdles race at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 14 [Package093_009])
    - Sports Day — Hurdles race at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 14 [Package093_011])
    - Sports Day — Long jump event at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 39 [Box273_017])
    - Sports Day — Long jump event at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 14 [Package093_002])
    - Sports Day — Long jump event at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 14 [Package093_007])
    - Sports Day — Long jump event at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 14 [Package093_012])
    - Sports Day — Long jump event at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 18 [package102])
    - Sports Day — Long jump event at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 18 [package102b])
    - Sports Day — Long jump event at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 18 [package102c])
    - Sports Day — Long jump event at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 18 [package102d])
    - Sports Day — Long jump event at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 18 [package102k])
    - Sports Day — Running race at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 18 [package102j])
    - Sports Day — Running race at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 18 [package102l])
    - Sports Day — Running race at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 18 [package102m])
    - Sports Day — Student at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 14 [Package093_008])
    - Sports Day — Students at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 14 [Package093_003])
    - Sports Day — Students at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 14 [Package093_005])
    - Sports Day — Students at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 14 [Package093_006])
    - Sports Day — Students at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 14 [Package093_010])
    - Sports Day — Students at Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 14 [Package093_014])
    - Sports Day — Vassar's lacrosse team and the Women's New York Lacrosse Association's team on Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 14 [Package093_004])
    - Sports Day — Vassar's lacrosse team and the Women's New York Lacrosse Association's team on Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 18 [package102e])
    - Sports Day — Vassar's lacrosse team and the Women's New York Lacrosse Association's team on Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 18 [package102i])
    - Sports Day — Vassar's lacrosse team playing the Women's New York Lacrosse Association's team on Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 18 [package102f])
    - Sports Day — Vassar's lacrosse team playing the Women's New York Lacrosse Association's team on Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 18 [package102g])
    - Sports Day — Vassar's lacrosse team playing the Women's New York Lacrosse Association's team on Sports Day, 1932 May 7 (Box 18 [package102h])
    - Sports Day — High jump event at Sports Day, 1934 May 12 (Box 8 [Package035_002])
    - Sports Day — Hurdles race at Sports Day, 1934 May 12 (Box 8 [Package035_007])
    - Sports Day — Long jump event at Sports Day, 1934 May 12 (Box 8 [Package035_001])
    - Sports Day — Rena "Betty" Buck (VC 1934) and Frances Preston (VC 1934) with the Sports Day cup, 1934 May 12 (Box 8 [Package035_004])
    - Sports Day — Rena "Betty" Buck (VC 1934), Frances Preston (VC 1934), and Alice Egan (VC 1937) with the Sports Day cup, 1934 May 12 (Box 8 [Package035_005])
    - Sports Day — Running race at Sports Day, 1934 May 12 (Box 8 [Package035_006])
    - Sports Day — Throwing event at Sports Day, 1934 May 12 (Box 8 [Package035_003])
    - Sports Day — Group portrait of golfers from the Dutchess County Women's Association on Sports Day, 1936 May 9 (Box 9 [Package038_007])
    - Sports Day — Group portrait of Vassar's Sports Day golfers, 1936 May 9 (Box 9 [Package038_006])
    - Sports Day — High jump event at Sports Day, 1936 May 9 (Box 9 [Package038_001])
    - Sports Day — Javelin throw event at Sports Day, 1936 May 9 (Box 9 [Package038_002])
    - Sports Day — Javelin throw event at Sports Day, 1936 May 9 (Box 23 [package117n])
    - Sports Day — Lacrosse game on Sports Day, 1936 May 9 (Box 37/38 [Box271_012])
    - Sports Day — Long jump event at Field Day, 1936 May 9 (Box 9 [Package038_005])
    - Sports Day — Running race at Sports Day, 1936 May 9 (Box 23 [package117m])
    - Sports Day — Vassar's golfers and Dutchess County Women's Association golfers mingling during the Sports Day competition, 1936 May 9 (Box 9 [Package038_008])
  - Tennis
    - Tennis player — Unidentified student playing on the tennis courts, 1921 Oct (Box 27 [package152f])
    - Tennis player — Unidentified student playing on the tennis courts, 1921 Oct (Box 27 [package152i])
    - Tennis player — Unidentified student playing on the tennis courts, 1921 Oct (Box 29 [package157b])
  - Track
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1916 track team with Field Day banner, 1916-1917 (Box 92/93 [Box252_007])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1917 track team, 1916-1917 (Box 92 [Box251_004])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1917 track team, 1916-1917 (Box 92 [Box251_024])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1918 track team, 1916-1917 (Box 91/92 [Box250_002])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1919 track team, 1916-1917 (Box 92 [Box251_001])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1917 track team, 1917-1918 (Box 63 [203_16])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1919 track team, 1917-1918 (Box 92 [Box251_008])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1920 track team, 1917-1918 (Box 92 [Box251_006])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1921 track team with the Field Day banner, 1919-1920 (Box 57 [package138c])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1922 track team, 1919-1920 (Box 57 [package138i])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1922 track team with Field Day cup and banner, approximately 1920 (Box 73/74 [222_20])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1921 track team (Box 66 [208_03])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1921 track team (Box 66 [208_15])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1921 track team (Box 66 [208_16])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1921 track team (Box 66 [208_19])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1922 track team with Field Day cup and banner, 1921 (Box 66 [208_02])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1922 track team with Field Day cup and banner, 1921 (Box 66 [208_20])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1924 track team, 1921 (Box 73/74 [222_04])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1924 track team, 1921 (Box 73/74 [222_18])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1924 track team, 1921 (Box 73/74 [222_19])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1922 track team with Field Day banner, 1922-1923 (Box 69 [213_23])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1923 track team, 1922-1923 (Box 69 [213_03])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1923 track team, 1922-1923 (Box 69 [213_08])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1924 track team, 1922-1923 (Box 69 [213_01])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1924 track team, 1922-1923 (Box 69 [213_12])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1925 track team, 1922-1923 (Box 69 [213_02])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1923 track team, 1923-1924 (Box 53 [Package65_001])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1924 track team, 1923-1924 (Box 53 [Package65_003])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1924 track team, 1923-1924 (Box 53 [Package65_004])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1925 track team with Field Day banner, 1923-1924 (Box 53 [Package65_007])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1926 track team, 1923-1924 (Box 53 [Package65_002])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1924 track team (Box 49 [Package52_004])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1924 track team (Box 49 [Package52_005])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1924 track team (Box 49 [Package53_005])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1925 track team with Field Day banner, 1924 (Box 93/94 [Box253_024])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1925 track team with Field Day banner, 1924 (Box 49 [Package52_006])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1926 track team, 1924 (Box 49 [Package53_002])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1927 track team, 1924 (Box 49 [Package52_002])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1927 track team, 1924 (Box 49 [Package53_001])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1929 track team, 1926-1927 (Box 93/94 [Box253_023])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1927 track team (Box 70/71 [216_16])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1929 track team, 1928-1929 (Box 92/93 [Box252_023])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1930 track team with Field Day banner, 1928-1929 (Box 92/93 [Box252_004])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1930 track team, 1928-1929 (Box 92/93 [Box252_003])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1931 track team, 1928-1929 (Box 92/93 [Box252_024])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1930 track team, 1929 (Box 52 [Package62_009])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1930 track team, 1929 (Box 52 [Package62_010])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1930 track team, 1929 (Box 52 [Package62_011])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1930 track team, 1929 (Box 52 [Package64_007])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1931 track team, 1929 (Box 52 [Package62_001])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1931 track team, 1929 (Box 52 [Package64_001])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1931 track team, 1929 (Box 52 [Package64_009])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1932 track team, 1929 (Box 52 [Package62_004])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1932 track team, 1929 (Box 52 [Package64_006])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1931 track team, 1931-1932 (Box 47 [Package43_001])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1931 track team, 1931-1932 (Box 47 [Package43_006])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1932 track team, 1931-1932 (Box 47 [Package43_004])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1933 track team, 1931-1932 (Box 47 [Package43_002])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1933 track team, 1931-1932 (Box 47 [Package43_007])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1934 track team, 1931-1932 (Box 47 [Package43_010])
    - Track team portrait — Group of track team members, perhaps on Field Day, 1932 (Box 73/74 [222_06])
    - Track team portrait — Group of track team members, perhaps on Field Day, 1932 (Box 92 [Box251_005])
    - Track team portrait — Group of track team members, perhaps on Field Day, 1932 (Box 92 [Box251_009])
    - Track team portrait — Group of track team members, perhaps on Field Day, 1932 (Box 92 [Box251_019])
    - Track team portrait — Track team, 1933 (Box 73/74 [222_07])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1934 track team (Box 47 [Package43_008])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1936 track team, 1934 (Box 47 [Package43_005])
    - Track team portrait — Class of 1936 track team, 1934 (Box 47 [Package43_011])
    - Track team portrait — Unidentified class track team, 1934 (Box 47 [Package43_003])
    - Track team portrait — Unidentified class track team, 1934 (Box 47 [Package43_009])
  - Vassar Horse Show
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 15 [Package095_001])
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 15 [Package095_002])
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 15 [Package095_003])
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 15 [Package095_004])
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 15 [Package095_005])
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 15 [Package095_006])
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 15 [Package095_008])
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 15 [Package095_011])
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 15 [Package095_013])
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 16 [Package097_002])
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 16 [Package097_004])
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 19 [package106c])
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 19 [package106d])
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 19 [package106e])
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 24/25 [package121 l])
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 42/43 [Box278_009])
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 42/43 [Box278_010])
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 42/43 [Box278_016])
    - Vassar Horse Show — First annual horse show, held at Gray's Greenvale Farm, 1929 May 18 (Box 42/43 [Box278_018])
  - Water Basketball
    - Water Basketball team portrait — Varsity water basketball team, 1922-1923 (Box 92/93 [Box252_019])
    - Water basketball team portrait — Varsity water basketball team, approximately 1923 (Box 70/71 [216_22])
    - Water basketball team portrait — Varsity water basketball team. Mary K. Marshall (VC 1926), team manager, is in the back row, left, 1925-1926 (Box 77/78 [229_17])
  - Winter Carnival
    - Winter Carnival — Ice skaters on what appears to be Sunset Lake. May or may not be Winter Carnival, Early 1920s (Box 24/25 [package 121b])
    - Winter Carnival — Ice skaters on what appears to be Sunset Lake. May or may not be Winter Carnival, 1921-1925 (Box 44 [Box280_008])
    - Winter Carnival — Ice skaters on Sunset lake during Winter Carnival, 1922 Jan 14 (Box 19 [package106b])
    - Winter Carnival — One of the judges of the carnival, standing on Sunset Lake, 1922 Jan 14 (Box 44 [Box280_007])
    - Winter Carnival — Snow ball fight near Sunset lake during Winter Carnival, 1922 Jan 14 (Box 38 [Box272_018])
    - Winter Carnival — Snow ball fight near Sunset lake during Winter Carnival, 1922 Jan 14 (Box 19 [package106])
    - Winter Carnival — Student skating on Sunset Lake for the Winter Carnival exhibition, 1922 Jan 14 (Box 44 [Box280_019])
    - Winter Carnival — Students snowshoeing on Sunset Hill during the Winter Carnival, 1922 Jan 14 (Box 44 [Box280_020])
- Series II. Buildings and Grounds, 1897-1940
  - Alumnae House
    - Alumnae House groundbreaking — Blanch Ferry Hooker (VC 1894) and Queene Ferry Coonley (VC 1896) wielding the spade at the groundbreaking for Alumnae House, 1921 Jun 20 (Box 7 [Package030_003])
    - Alumnae House groundbreaking — Blanch Ferry Hooker (VC 1894) and Queene Ferry Coonley (VC 1896) wielding the spade at the groundbreaking for Alumnae House, 1921 Jun 20 (Box 7 [Package030_006])
    - Alumnae House groundbreaking — Ground breaking for Alumnae House. Blanch Ferry Hooker (VC 1894) is speaking. Her sister, Queene Ferry Coonley (VC 1896), is seated with an unidentified woman, 1921 Jun 20 (Box 10 [Package079_006])
    - Alumnae House groundbreaking — Ground breaking for Alumnae House. Queene Ferry Coonley (VC 1896) is speaking. Her sister, Blanch Ferry Hooker (VC 1894) is seated with an unidentified woman, 1921 Jun 20 (Box 7 [Package030_007])
    - Alumnae House groundbreaking — Groundbreaking for Alumnae House. Blanch Ferry Hooker (VC 1894) and Queene Ferry Coonley (VC 1896), the building's donors, are seated, 1921 Jun 20 (Box 3 [Package015_005])
    - Alumnae House groundbreaking — Procession to the "Rock Lot" for the Alumnae House groundbreaking, 1921 Jun 20 (Box 4 [Package020_008])
    - Alumnae House — Alumnae House soon after completion in 1924, approximately 1924 (Box 36 [Box269_009])
    - Alumnae House sketch — Copy photograph of a sketch of Alumnae House dated 1932, 1932-1940 (Box 37 [Box270_004])
    - Alumnae House sketch — Copy photograph of a sketch of Alumnae House dated 1932, 1932-1940 (Box 37 [Box270_024])
  - Blodgett Hall
    - Blodgett Hall — View of the euthenics building arch, approximately 1929 (Box 37 [Box270_013])
    - Blodgett Hall — View of the euthenics building arch, approximately 1929 (Box 36 [Box269_018])
  - Campus Grounds
    - Athletic Circle — Circle of land at the north end of campus, used for track and field, basketball, and other sports. Either Strong House or Lathrop is visible in the background, 1900-1920 (Box 31 [Box261_020])
    - Athletic Circle garden — Plot of irises in the gardens surrounding the Athletic Circle, 1900-1940 (Box 35/36 [Box268_020])
    - Bridge near Sunset Lake — Wooden bridge leading to path around Sunset Lake, 1910-1940 (Box 36 [Box269_001])
    - Campus viewed from Sunset Hill — View from Sunset Hill of the tops of buildings as well as the power plant chimney, 1909-1938 (Box 36 [Box269_026])
    - Campus viewed from Sunset Hill — View from Sunset Hill of the tops of buildings. Cropped version of Box269_026, 1909-1938 (Box 37 [Box270_019])
    - Faculty houses on Raymond Avenue — Faculty houses on Raymond Avenue while it was still a dirt road. Includes current houses numbered 81, 83, 85 and 87, 1905-1915 (Box 24/25 [package 121])
    - Man on Sunset Lake bridge — Man standing on the wooden bridge on the north end of Sunset Lake, 1910-1915 (Box 37 [Box270_020])
    - Outdoor Amphitheater — Performance space between Sanders Hall and Sunset late, approximately 1917 (Box 79/80 [233_09])
    - Outdoor Amphitheater — Performance space between Sanders Hall and Sunset late, approximately 1917 (Box 79/80 [233_23])
    - Rushing stream — Stream, possibly the Casperkill or Fonteynkill, 1910-1940 (Box 37/38 [Box271_020])
    - Sunset Hill, Vassar College — View of the land on the east side of the campus, 1907-1911 (Box 69 [214_01])
    - Taylor Gate — View of Taylor Gate from Raymond Avenue, 1910-1940 (Box 36 [Box269_007])